Finding Aid for Vice Provost for Academic and Multicultural Affairs (University of Michigan) records, 1970-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- General Files
  - University of Michigan Files
    - Racism
      - Incidents of Racism
        - General
          - 1987-1991, 1 folders (Box 12)
        - Arab American Students, 1989 (Box 12)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2064 ]
        - WJJX Radio Station, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
      - Petition Drive Against Racist Fliers, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Racist Fliers
        - 1987-1988, 1 folders (Box 8)
        - 1987-1988, 1 folders (Box 12)
    - Recruitment, Minority, 1987-1991 (Box 8)
    - Regents, 1987-1992 (Box 8)
    - Reserve Officer Training Corps (ROTC), 1987-1991 (Box 8)
    - Retention, Minority, 1987-1991 (Box 8)
    - Salary Equity Study, 1990 (Box 8)
    - Scholarships and Fellowships, Minority, 1984; 1991 (Box 8)
    - Schools and Colleges
      - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
        - General, 1987-1991 (Box 8)
        - Personnel, 1988 (Box 12)
        - Students, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
      - Art, School of, 1987-1990 (Box 8)
      - Athletics, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
      - Business Administration, School of, 1987-1992 (Box 8)
      - Dentistry, School of
        - 1987-1991, 1 folders (Box 12)
        - 1987-1991, 1 folders (Box 12)
      - Education, School of
        - General, 1987-1992 (Box 8)
        - Higher and Postsecondary Education, Center for the Study of, 1990 (Box 8)
        - Personnel, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
        - Students, 1989-1991 (Box 12)
      - Engineering, College of
        - General, 1987-1993; 2 folders (Box 9)
        - Detroit Area Precollege Engineering Program (DAPCEP), 1985-1991 (Box 9)
        - Personnel, 1990 (Box 12)
        - Students, 1987 (Box 12)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2062 ]
      - English Composition Board, 1988-1991 (Box 9)
      - Information and Library Studies, School of, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
      - Law, School of
        - 1987-1991, 1 folders (Box 9)
        - 1987-1991, 1 folders (Box 12)
      - Literature, Science, and the Arts, College of
        - General
          - General, 1987-1990 (Box 9)
          - Personnel, 1987 (Box 12)
          - Students, 1987; 1989 (Box 12)
        - Biology, Department of, 1987-1992
          - General, 1987-1992 (Box 9)
          - Personnel, 1987 (Box 12)
          - Students, 1992 (Box 12)
            [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2067 ]
        - Chemistry, Department of
          - Personnel, 1990-1991 (Box 12)
          - Students, 1989 (Box 12)
        - Classical Studies, Department of, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
        - Communication, Department of, 1988-1991
          - General, 1988-1991 (Box 9)
          - Personnel, 1988-1990; 2 folders (Box 12)
        - Economics, Department of
          - Personnel, 1988 (Box 12)
          - Students, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
        - English, Department of
          - General, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
          - Students, 1987; 1989 (Box 12)
        - Geological Sciences, Department of, 1988 (Box 12)
        - Mathematics, Department of, 1987; 1989 (Box 9)
        - Political Science, Department of, 1987-1990 (Box 12)
        - Psychology, Department of
          - General, 1989; 1991 (Box 9)
          - Grievance, 1993 (Box 12)
            [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2023 ]
        - Sociology, Department of
          - General, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
          - Personnel, 1989 (Box 12)
          - Students, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
      - Medical School
        - General
          - Open, 1987-1992 (Box 9)
          - Personnel, 1987-1991 (Box 12)
          - Students, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
        - Human Resources Department, 1987-1989 (Box 9)
        - Inteflex Program
          - General, 1987-1990 (Box 9)
          - Students, 1989 (Box 12)
        - Student and Minority Affairs, Office of, 1987-1991
          - General, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
          - Restricted, 1989-1991 (Box 12)
      - Music, School of
        - General, 1987-1989 (Box 9)
        - Students, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - Natural Resources, School of
        - General, 1985-1992 (Box 9)
        - Personnel, 1991-1992 (Box 12)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2022 ]
      - Nursing, School of
        - General, 1987-1992 (Box 9)
        - Personnel, 1988 (Box 12)
      - Pharmacy, College of
        - General, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
        - Personnel, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - Public Health, School of
        - General, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
        - Students, 1988 (Box 12)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2063 ]
      - Rackham School of Graduate Studies
        - General, 1985-1991 (Box 9)
        - Students, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
      - Residential College Independent Study Project, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
      - Social Work, School of
        - General, 1987-1992 (Box 9)
        - Personnel, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
        - Students, 1988; 1990 (Box 12)
      - UM-Dearborn
        - General, 1987-1992 (Box 9)
        - Personnel, 1988-1992 (Box 12)
        - Students, 1987 (Box 12)
      - UM-Flint, 1987-1990 (Box 9)
    - Security, University, 1989-1991 (Box 10)
    - South African Initiatives, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Steiner, Peter O., 1987-1988 (Box 10)
    - Student Organizations
      - General, 1987-1993 (Box 10)
      - African American
        - General, 1984-1991 (Box 10)
        - Alpha Kappa Alpha (macing incident), 1990-1991 (Box 10)
        - Black Student Union (BSU), 1984-1991 (Box 10)
      - Asian American, 1988-1991 (Box 10)
      - Hispanic, 1987-1991 (Box 10)
      - Michigan Student Assembly, 1986-1989 (Box 10)
      - Native American, 1987-1991 (Box 10)
      - United Coalition Against Racism (UCAR)
        - General, 1987-1989 (Box 10)
        - Restricted, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
    - Trotter House, 1987-1990 (Box 10)
    - Undergraduate Initiatives Fund Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 10)
    - University Relations, Office of, 1989; 1991 (Box 10)
    - Women, 1987-1990 (Box 10)
  - 1981-1993
    - Advisory Committee (VPMA), 1991-1992 (Box 13)
    - Advisory Committee on Undergraduate Admissions, 1987; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Africenergy (student organization), 1992 (Box 13)
    - American Council on Education (survey), 1992 (Box 13)
    - Association of Black Professional Administrators, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Black Issues in Higher Education (teleconference), 1992 (Box 13)
    - Black Student Union, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Center for Educational Improvement through Collaboration (CEIC), 1990-1991 (Box 13)
    - Collaborative Programs, 1988-1992 (Box 13)
    - Commission on Minority Student Recruitment, Success, and Graduation, 1989-1994 (Box 13)
    - Committee to Review University Programs on Minority Affairs, 1991/92 (Box 13)
    - Community Colleges
      - General, 1987-1992 (Box 13)
      - Highland Park Community College, 1987-1992 (Box 13)
      - Washtenaw Community College, 1987-1991 (Box 13)
      - Wayne County Community College, 1987-1991 (Box 13)
    - Consortium to Identify and Promote Hispanic Professionals, 1992-1993 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1987; 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Council on Multicultural University (COMU)
      - General, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - Membership, 1992-1994 (Box 13)
      - Minutes, 1990-1992 (Box 13)
      - Success Stories, 1992; 2 folders (Box 13)
      - Tracking the Data (COMU subgroup), 1992 (Box 13)
    - Diabetes and the Black Population Task Force, 1989-1992 (Box 13)
    - Discrimination and Harassment, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
    - Diversity Retreat, 1986-1987 (Box 13)
    - Faculty of Color, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Faculty Recruitment and Retention, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Hispanic Heritage Month, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Historically Black Colleges and Universities, 1988-1992 (Box 14)
    - King/Chavez/Parks
      - Advisory Committee, 1988; 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Programs Report, 1986; 2 folders (Box 14)
      - Visiting Professorship Program, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
    - Martin Luther King Jr. Day Symposium
      - General, 1992 (Box 14)
      - Schedule, 1989-1992 (Box 14)
      - Survey (sampling), 1992 (Box 14)
      - Transcripts, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Mandate, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Michigan Study Interview of Individual Students and Focus Groups of, Fall 1990 (Box 14)
    - Minority and Tenured Faculty, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Minority Issues Briefing Book, 1986; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Paper
      - The Multicultural Organization, 1990 (Box 14)
    - Post Doctoral Fellowship, 1987 (Box 14)
    - Racism (re: WJJX incident), 1987 (Box 14)
    - Reports
      - 1981
        - Report of the College of Literature, Science and the Arts Minority Task Force (Box 14)
        - Report of the Task Force on Minority Student Concerns (Box 14)
      - 1982
        - Report on Minority Student Recruitment and Retention (Box 14)
      - 1983
        - The Housing Division Report on Minority Student Recruitment and Retention, 1982-83 (Box 14)
        - Student Retention and Academic Progress at the University of Michigan, Ann Arbor An Analysis of the Freshman Retention File Data, 1975-1981 (Box 14)
      - 1987
        - An Analysis of Productivity of Non-Tenured Underrepresented Minority Faculty Based on the Faculty Cohort Studies (Box 14)
        - Minority Undergraduate Student Retention at the University of Michigan: Creating Conditions for Success (Box 14)
      - 1988
        - Comments on Racism and Diversity (Box 14)
        - Minority Student Retention: A Preliminary Review of the Data (Box 14)
      - 1989
        - The Enrollment Decision Project A Retrospective Review, 1982-1986 (Box 14)
        - University Financial Aid Advisory Committee Undergraduate Merit Scholarship and Need-Based Award Program Recommendations (Box 14)
        - Update on Student Retention and Academic Progress at the University of Michigan, Ann Arbor An Analysis of the Freshman Retention File Data, 1978-1982 (Box 14)
      - 1990
        - The Minority Student in Engineering: A Review of the Retention Literature (Box 14)
      - 1992
        - Report of the Committee to Review University Programs in Minority Affairs and Services (Box 14)
    - Scholarships (minorities), 1992 (Box 14)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs, 1987-1989 (Box 14)
    - Speeches (Charles Moody)
      - Affirmative Action, undated (Box 14)
      - Founders Day Speech at Central State University, 1993 (Box 14)
    - Undergraduate Admissions, 1992 (Box 14)
    - University of Michigan Law School Minority Report, 1987; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Vice Provost for Academic Affairs, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
    - Vice Provost for the Office of Academic Multicultural Initiatives (position search), 1992 (Box 14)
    - Vice President for Research, Office of, (re: diversity), 1988 (Box 14)
  - 1989-1997
    - Academic Affairs
      - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 19)
      - Cultural Audit, 1994 (Box 19)
      - (8 + 1) Group, 1994-1995 (Box 19)
      - Hate Mail, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Internal Task Force, 1994 (Box 19)
      - Miscellaneous, 1993-1995 (Box 19)
      - Planning Effective Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 19)
      - Provost Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 19)
    - Academic Planning and Analysis
      - 1990-1995 (Box 19)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 19)
    - Academic Program Group, 1993-1995 (Box 19)
    - Academic Services Board, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Admissions
      - Advisory Committee, 1990 (Box 20)
      - Minority Admissions Data
        - 1994 (Box 20)
        - 1997-1998 (Box 20)
        - Medical School, Law School, and LS&A admissions data, 1996 (Box 20)
      - Office of, 1995 (Box 20)
      - Statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
      - Student of Color Recruitment, 1995-1996 (Box 20)
      - Undergraduate, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
    - Affirmative Action
      - General
        - 1993-1994 (Box 20)
        - 1995-1996 (Box 20)
        - 1996-1997 (Box 20)
      - Ad Hoc Committee
        - 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 20)
        - 1996-1997, 2 folders (Box 20)
      - Articles, 1996-1997 (Box 20)
      - General Counsel, 1996 (Box 41)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2096 ]
      - Pamphlets, Reports, etc., 1996-1997 (Box 20)
      - Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - State of Michigan Legislation, 1995-1996 (Box 20)
    - African American Art (Dr. and Mrs. Curtis), 1996 (Box 20)
    - African American community meeting, 1996 (Box 20)
    - African American Student Leadership Conference, 1993 (Box 20)
    - African American Studies Retreat Minutes, 1995 (Box 20)
    - Alumni
      - General, 1994-1995 (Box 20)
      - Black Alumni, 1996-1997 (Box 20)
    - Alumni Association, 1996 (Box 20)
    - American Council on Education, 1994 (Box 20)
    - Americans with Disabilities Act, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Ann Arbor Police Department, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival, 1996-1997 (Box 20)
    - Articles, Clippings and Press Releases, 1987-1996; 3 folders (Box 20)
    - Asian American Students, 1994 (Box 20)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1993 (Box 20)
    - Association of American Colleges and Universities
      - General, 1993-1997; 5 folders (Box 20)
      - American Commitments Curriculum, 1994-1995 (Box 21)
      - Conference, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Indiana State University, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
      - Michigan State University, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
      - North Dakota State University, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
    - Association for Black Professionals and Administrators
      - 1993 (Box 21)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 21)
    - Baker Mandela Center, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Black Action Movement 25th Anniversary, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Black Business Students Association, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Black Medical Association/National Medical Association, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Black Student Union
      - 1994-1995 (Box 21)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 21)
    - Black Students, 1994-1997 (Box 21)
    - Campus Climate, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Campus Climate Conference, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Campus Information Center, 1994 (Box 21)
    - Center for African and African-American Studies
      - 1993-1995 (Box 21)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 21)
    - Center for Continuing Education of Women, 1994-1995 (Box 21)
    - Center for Education of Women (CEW), 1992-1993 (Box 21)
    - Colleges and Universities
      - Indiana University, 1993 (Box 21)
      - Iowa State University, 1994 (Box 21)
      - Oakland University (Rochester, MI), 1993 (Box 21)
      - Southwest Texas State University, 1994 (Box 21)
      - State University of New York, 1993 (Box 21)
      - Tennessee State University, 1993 (Box 21)
      - University of Chicago, 1993 (Box 21)
      - University of South Carolina, 1993 (Box 21)
    - Committee of Recruiters
      - 1989-1991 (Box 21)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 21)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation
      - 1994-1995 (Box 21)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 21)
      - Meeting Materials, 1995-1996 (Box 21)
    - Committees (COMU, PACMA, SACUA), 1994-1995 (Box 21)
    - Community Colleges, 1993-1994 (Box 21)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program, 1992-1994 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence
      - 1993 (Box 21)
      - 1996 (Box 21)
    - Cultural Diversity Audit Project Documentation, January, 1992 (Box 21)
    - Dearborn-U-M Dearborn grievances, 1995 (Box 21)
    - Development, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
    - Diversity
      - General, 1996-1997 (Box 21)
      - Diversity Booklet, 1995 (Box 21)
      - Diversity Conferences and Seminars, 1993-1994 (Box 21)
      - Diversity Programs
        - Outside Companies, 1994 (Box 21)
        - Other Universities, 1991-1994 (Box 21)
        - Committee on Institutional Cooperation
          - 1994 (Box 22)
          - 1996-1997 (Box 22)
      - Ford Foundation Diversity Initiative Conference, 1996 (Box 22)
    - Education (General), 1993 (Box 22)
    - Education, Department of, 1996-1997 (Box 22)
    - Email hate mail incident, 1994 (Box 22)
    - Enrollment
      - 1994 (Box 22)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 22)
    - Events Office, 1996-1997 (Box 22)
    - Faculty-Minority Faculty Information
      - African American Faculty Association, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Faculty Awards Committee, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Faculty Equity Study, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Faculty Mentoring Report, 1996 (Box 22)
      - Faculty of Color
        - 1990-1996, 2 folders (Box 22)
        - Development Packet, 1995 (Box 22)
        - Development Survey, 1994 (Box 22)
        - Information Sessions on Faculty Awards, 1995 (Box 22)
        - Luncheon, 1993-1994 (Box 22)
        - Terminations, 1990-1995 (Box 22)
      - FairTeach (Faculty and Staff Against Institutional Racism Teaching Group), 1994; 2 folders (Box 22)
      - King Chavez Parks Visiting Professors Program, 1991-1994; 3 folders (Box 22)
      - Quality of the Climate for Minority Faculty Report, 1994 (Box 22)
      - Tenured Minority Faculty, 1984-1994 (Box 22)
      - TOO (Target of Opportunity Program), 1991-1994 (Box 22)
    - Faculty Affairs, 1990-1994 (Box 22)
    - Faculty Data, 1996-1997 (Box 22)
    - Faculty Development Survey, undated (Box 22)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 1994 (Box 22)
    - Financial Statements, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 23)
    - First Year Center, 1995 (Box 23)
    - First Year Experiences, 1993-1994 (Box 23)
    - Freedom of Information, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Gerontology, Institute of, 1994 (Box 23)
    - Goals and Objectives, 1991-1994 (Box 23)
    - Government Relations, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Grievances
      - General, 1996-1997 (Box 41)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2027 ]
      - Thomas Landefeld, 1993-1994 (Box 41)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2024 ]
    - High Schools, 1994 (Box 23)
    - Hispanic
      - 1993-1994 (Box 23)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Hispanic Association of Colleges and Universities
      - 1994 (Box 23)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Historically Black Colleges and Universities/Hispanic Serving Institutions/Native American Institutions Committee (HBCU/HSI/NAI)
      - Committee Members, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Correspondence, 1989-1990; 1993 (Box 23)
      - Initiatives, 1992-1993 (Box 23)
      - Lists of Participating Institutions, 1990-1991 (Box 23)
      - Partnership/Program Description Forms, 1992 (Box 23)
      - Resources, 1991 (Box 23)
      - Sub-Committee Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1992 (Box 23)
    - Honorary Degree Nomination, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Housing, University Housing Department, 1995-1996 (Box 23)
    - Human Resources and Affirmative Action, 1995 (Box 23)
    - Incentive Scholars Program (ISP), 1992-1993 (Box 23)
    - Information Technology Division
      - Director Search, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
      - Managing Diversity Program, 1994 (Box 23)
    - Institute for Public Policy (IPP), 1993-1994 (Box 23)
    - Institute for Social Research (ISR), 1993 (Box 23)
    - Intergroup Relations, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Invitations, 1993-1994 (Box 23)
    - Johnson Report, "Report of the of the Committee to Review Minority Affairs and Services,", 1992 (Box 23)
    - Lansing Servicing Center, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Latino Projects, 1995-1996
    - Lawrence Levine Evening at Rackham, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Leadership 2017, 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - Library, University
      - 1993-1994 (Box 23)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 23)
    - Medstart, 1995-1996 (Box 23)
    - Michigan Black Caucus, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Michigan Mandate
      - Five and six year progress reports, 1992-1993 (Box 23)
      - Analysis, 1994 (Box 23)
      - Council on a Multicultural-Cultural University Review, 1994; undated (Box 23)
    - Michigan Study (impact of diversity efforts)
      - 1992-1993 (Box 23)
      - 1994 (Box 23)
    - Midwest Consortium for Latino Research
      - 1993 (Box 23)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 23)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 23)
    - "Mini-Conference" on African Cultural Awareness, 1991-1992 (Box 23)
    - Minority Affairs Programs, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Minority Enrollment Articles, 1992-1993 (Box 23)
    - Minority Equity-Michigan Department of Education, 1992-1994 (Box 24)
    - Minority Opportunity Summer Training (MOST) Report, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Minority Scholarship, 1992-1993 (Box 24)
    - Minority Student Initiatives Meeting, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Minority Student Services, 1992-1993 (Box 24)
    - Minority Youth Mentor Program, 1995-1996 (Box 24)
    - MLK, 1993-1996 (Box 24)
    - MORE (Michigan Opportunities for Research Experience) Steering Committee, 1996 (Box 24)
    - Multicultural Society Theme Semester, 1993-1994 (Box 24)
    - Multicultural University Conference, 1993-1994 (Box 24)
    - Museum of Art
      - Community Programs (includes photos), 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 24)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 24)
      - 1994 (Box 24)
    - M-Quality, 1994 (Box 24)
    - National Alliance of Black School Educators
      - 1994 (Box 24)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 24)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 24)
    - National Association for Equal Opportunity in Higher Education
      - 1993 (Box 24)
      - 1994-1995 (Box 24)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP)
      - 1993 (Box 24)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 24)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 24)
    - National Black Law Students Association, 1994-1995 (Box 24)
    - National Science Foundation, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Native American Students, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Negro-Caucasian Club, 1995-1996 (Box 24)
    - Network America Study Data, 1995 (Box 24)
    - News and Information, 1995-1996 (Box 24)
    - Nichols and Associates (re: Medical School Cultural Diversity Assessment proposal), 1994 (Box 24)
    - North Carolina Alliance for Minority Participation in Engineering and Science (N-CAMP) visit, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Office of Orientation
      - General Files, 1989-1992; 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Director's (Pamela Horne) Files
        - 1989-1992 (Box 24)
        - 1993-1994 (Box 24)
      - National Orientation Directors Association Conference, 1994 (Box 24)
      - Parents Diversity Workshop (Box 24)
      - Students of Color Visitation, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Pastor's Alliance, 1994 (Box 41)
    - Personnel-Jacina Davis, 1992-1994 (Box 41)
    - President, Office of, 1995 (Box 24)
    - President's Advisory Commission on Multicultural Affairs (PACMA)
      - Agendas and Minutes, 1992-1994 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence, 1990-1994 (Box 24)
      - Goals: Report, ca., 1990 (Box 24)
      - Membership Lists, 1993-1995 (Box 24)
    - President's Advisory Commission on Women (PACWI), 1995 (Box 24)
    - Press Releases, 1994 (Box 24)
    - Proctor & Gamble, 1995 (Box 25)
    - Program on Conflict Management Alternatives (PCMA), 1993 (Box 25)
    - Proposals
      - 1994 (Box 25)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 25)
    - Public Health Students of African Descent (PHSAD), 1993 (Box 25)
    - Public Safety, 1995-1996 (Box 25)
    - Public Schools
      - Ann Arbor
        - Huron High School, 1994 (Box 25)
      - Detroit
        - Detroit Pre-College Engineering Program, 1992-1995 (Box 25)
        - High School, 1994 (Box 25)
        - Impact Seminar for Youth (Finney High School), 1992 (Box 25)
        - Mackenzie High School, 1994 (Box 25)
        - Urban Systematic Initiatives, 1994 (Box 25)
      - State of Michigan Department of Education
        - General, 1992-1995 (Box 25)
        - Minority Equity Fund, 1994 (Box 25)
    - Racism (Bibliography) (Box 25)
    - Racism-Student Complaints, 1994 (Box 25)
    - Recruitment and Retention
      - 1993-1994 (Box 25)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 25)
    - Regents (University of Michigan)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 25)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 25)
    - Reports
      - "The Michigan Agenda for Women :Leadership for a New Century,", 1994 (Box 25)
      - "Task Force on the First-Year Experience,", 1994 (Box 25)
      - "Women at the University of Michigan,", 1994 (Box 25)
    - Secretary of the University, 1995-1996 (Box 25)
    - Seminars and Conferences, 1992-1993 (Box 25)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA)
      - 1993-1994 (Box 25)
      - 1994-1996 (Box 25)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 25)